[Waco] L.L. Sams Stained Glass Studio records, Inclusive: 1952-1992, Bulk: 1970-1985
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
[Waco] L.L. Sams Stained Glass Studio records
Inclusive: 1952-1992, Bulk: 1970-1985
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3223
L.L. Sams Stained Glass Studio
6 document boxes, 4 OVZ boxes, and 9 OVZ folders
The L. L. Sams Stained Glass Studio records include project files, renderings, and slides that document the creation and installation of stained glass windows in Texas institutions such as churches, schools, and military installations. Correspondence, sketches, photographs, product samples, oversize drawings, and colored renderings are included.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The L.L. Sams and Sons Company was founded in 1898 by L.L Sams. He was the first Texas sales representative for the E.H. Stafford company located in Michigan. Sams and Sons Company was strictly a sales agency until 1946 when they began manufacturing their own products.
As clientele, needs, and trends evolved, the L.L. Sams and Sons Company began to branch out as well. They began by creating a separate manufacturing division, followed by church renovations, stained glass production, and several other endeavors through the years. The L.L. Sams Stained Glass Studio began in 1965 with three artists: Robert Mansfield, Ron Estep, and Annabelle Estep. Ron Estep created one of the studio's largest pieces, a 1,000 square foot panel depicting the life of Jesus Christ through symbols. The window was commissioned by Grove Avenue Baptist Church in Richmond, Virginia, and took over one year to complete.
The studio created high quality pieces utilizing the dalle de verre technique, a mixture of sand and epoxy to fit the glass together instead of the traditional lead. While the studio began only servicing religious institutions, as requests slowed, they took on projects from schools, restaurants, military installations, and other entities. When the larger L. L. Sams and Sons Company merged with the Royal Seating Company the Stained Glass Studio dissolved and sold their remaining glass inventory to Bryant Stanton of Stanton Glass studio, located in Waco, Texas.
Scope and Content
[Waco] L.L. Sams Stained Glass Studio records contain three series: I. Project Files, II. Renderings, and III. Slides. Project Files highlight the preparation and business aspects of creating a stained glass piece. Correspondence and financial agreements comprise a good portion of this series, but drawings and sketches portray the preparation needed before creation. Oversize drafts and architectural prints illustrate installations and provide a guide for size and colors utilized in final production.
The Renderings series contains colored scale drawings of pieces installed in churches and military installations. Some include notes for improvements suggesting that clients were included in the planning stages. These renderings often match up with project files, but not all will have corresponding data.
Slides are representative of the creation and installation process of stained glass window making. The slides depict the maker process from design to installation.
Arrangement
The collection was previously arranged into boxes based on material type and size. Project files were arranged alphabetically by site location while renderings and slides had no formal arrangement. The collection is now arranged into three series: I. Project Files, II. Renderings, and III. Slides.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3223. Acquired 1997-06-00
Related Resources
Items in related collections
[Waco] L.L. Sams and Sons Company records, Inclusive: 1824-1995, undated, Bulk: 1948-1989, undated
Related references
Bakke, Bruce B. “Church Renovation Calls for Special Skills in Craftsmanship -- and in Selling: ‘You Don’t Talk to an Evangelist the Same Way You Talk to a Monsignor’.” United Press International. 1984 August 26. Accessed 2020 February 3.
Fredensprung, Amanda. “Stained-Glass Wizard: Meet the Man Behind the Creations of Stanton Glass Studio.” Waco Tribune-Herald (Waco, TX), 2013 February 28. Accessed 2020 February 3.
“Good Pews for Modern Man.” Texas Monthly. 1979 November.
Smith, Daniel. “Living in the Past.” Focus Magazine. 2015 November 29. Accessed 2020 February 3.
Index Terms
Subjects
Business enterprises -- Texas -- Waco.; Stained glass windows.
Genres
Architectural drawings.; Business correspondence.; Financial records.; Photographs.; Slides (photographs)
- Project Files, 1952-1992, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Project Files series is dated 1952-1992, and includes preliminary sketches, detail and process drawings, correspondence, contracts, purchase orders (with additional notes), and estimates. Also included are installation photographs in the form of slides, polaroid and 35mm prints. Occasional fabric samples are present as well. The series retained original order, alphabetical by site location, and is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  35 mm slide; Instant color print; Photographic print
  - Abbott, TX: Immaculate Heart of Mary, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abilene, TX: Mac’s Drivateria, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arlington, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Austin, TX: Bergstrom Air Force Base, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Austin, TX: University Avenue Church of Christ, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bay City, TX: Holy Cross, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bay City, TX: First Presbyterian Church, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bellmead, TX: La Vega High School, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breckenridge, TX: St. Andrew’s Episcopal, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brownfield, TX: First Baptist Church, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brownwood, TX: First Baptist Church, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bruceville, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Burkburnett, TX: First Baptist Church, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Burnet, TX: First United Methodist, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Carthage, TX: Ebenezer United Methodist Church, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Center City, TX: Center City Methodist, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chester, TX: Cade Memorial Methodist, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chester, TX: First Baptist Church, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Clifton, TX: First Presbyterian (1 of 2), 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Clifton, TX: First Presbyterian (2 of 2), 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Clifton, TX: First Methodist, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - College Station, TX: Aldersgate United Methodist Church, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Colorado City, TX: All Saints Episcopal Church, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Columbus, TX: St. John’s Episcopal, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Conroe, TX: First Presbyterian Church, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Conroe, TX: Montgomery Company Medical Hospital Center, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Corsicana, TX: First Baptist Church, 1972-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cranfills Gap, TX: St. Olaf Lutheran Church (1 of 2), 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cranfills Gap, TX: St. Olaf Lutheran Church (2 of 2), 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Crowley, TX: St. Francis Retirement Village-Protestant Chapel, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cypress-Fairbanks, TX: Christ United Church, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dallas, TX: Cliff Temple Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dallas, TX: Cliff Temple Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dallas, TX: Congregation Shearith-Israel, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dallas, TX: Don Dixon, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dallas, TX: Restland Mausoleum, 1968-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Denton, TX: Classic Stained Glass (Jenny Sewell), undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Diana, TX: First Baptist Church, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Farmersville, TX: First Baptist Church, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Friona, TX: First Methodist Church, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Friona, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fort Hood, TX: First Cavalry, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fort Worth, TX: First Pentecostal Church, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fort Worth, TX: Pentecostal Church of God in Christ, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Galveston, TX: Central Christian Church, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Gatesville, TX: Coryell Memorial Hospital, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown, TX: First Baptist Church, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown, TX: Southwestern University Chapel, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Giddings, TX: Immanuel Lutheran, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Glass Samples, Casimir Collection, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Graham, TX: Graham General Hospital, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Groves, TX: First Baptist Church, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Halfway, TX: First Baptist Church, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Harlingen, TX: First Baptist Church, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Harlingen, TX: First Presbyterian, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Harlingen, TX: Immaculate Heart of Mary, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Harlingen, TX: St. Anthony Catholic Church, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hart, TX: First Baptist (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hart, TX: First Baptist (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hempstead, TX: St. Bartholomew’s Episcopal, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hereford, TX: First Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hereford, TX: First Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hereford, TX: St. Thomas Episcopal Church, 1973-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hitchcock, TX: First Baptist Church, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Hooks, TX: First Baptist Church, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Houston, TX: Garden Villas Baptist Church, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Houston, TX: Hope Will Baptist, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Houston, TX: Mount Pleasant Baptist, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Houston, TX: St. John’s Lutheran, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Houston, TX: Wilcrest Baptist Church, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Houston, TX: Zion Lutheran Church, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Inez, TX: St. Joseph’s Catholic Church, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jacksonville, TX: First Baptist Church, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Jacksonville, TX: First United Methodist, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Jewett, TX: Jewett Methodist Church (1 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Jewett, TX: Jewett Methodist Church (2 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jewett, TX: Judy Hastings, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kermit, TX: First Baptist Church, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LaGrange, TX: First Baptist Church, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lamesa, TX: First Methodist, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Laredo, TX: Blessed Sacrament Church, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Levelland, TX: First Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Levelland, TX: First Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lewisville, TX: Macedonia Baptist, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Liberty, TX: Yettie Kersting Memorial Hospital, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lorena, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Lubbock, TX: P.P.G. Industries, Incorporated (Lubbock Company Teaching Hospital), 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lyford, TX: Prince of Peace Church, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Madisonville, TX: First Baptist Church, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Madisonville, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Malone, TX: Salem Lutheran, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Marshal, TX: First Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1977-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Marshal, TX: First Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1977-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - McAllen, TX: Zonta Club of W. Hidalgo Company, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mesquite, TX: East Ridge Park Christian, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Midland, TX: The Episcopal Church of the Holy Trinity, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nacogdoches, TX: Redeemer Lutheran Church, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Nocona, TX: Bethel Baptist Church, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Odessa, TX: Cumberland Presbyterian, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Odessa, TX: First United Methodist Church, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Odessa, TX: Lutheran Church of the Risen Lord, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Odessa, TX: Oliver’s Restaurant, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Odessa, TX: St. Barnabas Episcopal, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Orange, TX: Philip Hobbs (Mesa Industries Incorporated), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Palestine, TX: South Side Baptist Church, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pampa, TX: First Baptist Church, 1967-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pampa, Tx: First Presbyterian, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pampa, TX: Mary Ellen and Harvester Church of Christ, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pasadena, TX: First United Methodist Church (1 of 2), 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pasadena, TX: First United Methodist Church (2 of 2), 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pasadena, TX: St. Peter’s Episcopal Church, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Plainview, TX: College Heights Baptist, 1971-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Plano, TX: Prairie Creek Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Port Arthur, TX: Saint George’s Episcopal, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Port Arthur, TX: St. Joseph’s Church, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Port Neches, TX: First Baptist, 1972-1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Refugio, TX: First Baptist Church, 1970-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Richmond, TX: Church of the Sacred Heart, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Roanoke, TX: E & S Manufacturing, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Robinson, TX: Calvary Assembly of God, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rockdale, TX: First Presbyterian Church, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rockwood, Tennessee: First Christian, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - San Antonio, TX: Shearer Hills Baptist Church, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - San Antonio, TX: Saint Mathew’s Parish, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - San Antonio, TX: Woodlawn Associates, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Shiner, TX: S.S. Cyril and Methodious Catholic Church, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Slaton, TX: First Baptist Church, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Stamford, TX: First Baptist Church, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Stanton, TX: First Baptist Church, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sweetwater, TX: St. Steven’s Episcopal Church, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Temple, TX: First Baptist Church, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Temple, TX: First Baptist Church, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Texarkana, TX: First Baptist Church, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tulia, TX: Central Church of Christ, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Tulia, TX: First Baptist Church, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Tyler, TX: First Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, TX: First Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Vernon, TX: Grace Episcopal Church, 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Victoria, TX: Baptist Temple, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Waco, TX: Armstrong-Browning Library, Baylor University, 1952-1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Waco, TX: Baylor University, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Waco, TX: Brookview Methodist Church, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Waco, TX: Cogdell Memorial United Methodist Church, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Waco, TX: Herring Avenue Methodist Church, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Waco, TX: Lakewood Christian Church, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Waco, TX: Linden Coone Construction Company (Pepper’s), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Waco, TX: Mosley Machinery Company, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Waco, TX: St. Mathew’s Lutheran Church, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Waco, TX: Trinity Church, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Waco, TX: Western Heights Baptist Church, 1975-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Wheeler, TX: First Methodist Church (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, TX: First Methodist Church (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Womack, TX: Zion United Church of Christ, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Renderings, 1968-1982, undated; 2
  The Renderings series is mostly undated; however, pieces can be cross-referenced with Project Files to obtain further information accordingly. Scale drawings of glass projects are present, some with notes documenting corrections and improvements to adjust before preparation. Items are listed alphabetically by site location, but physically they are arranged by size. This series is in good condition.
  - Abbott, TX: Immaculate Heart of Mary, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Amarillo, TX: Northwest Texas Hospital Chapel, 1982 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Arlington, TX: First Methodist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Austin, TX: Bergstrom Air Force Base Chapel, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Austin, TX: The World of Pentecost, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Austin, TX: Ward Memorial Chapel, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Baytown, TX: Mount Rose Missionary Baptist Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Beaumont, TX: St. Mark’s Episcopal, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Beaumont, TX: St. Mark’s Episcopal, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Beaumont, TX: St. Mark’s Episcopal Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Brownfield, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Brownsville, TX: St. Mary’s Catholic Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Bryan, TX: Shiloh Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Burnet, TX: The First Christian Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Chester, TX: Cade Memorial Methodist Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Chester, TX: Enon Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Clifton, TX: First Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - College Station, TX: Grace Bible Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Corpus Christi, TX: Seaside Mausoleum, 1969 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Dallas, TX: Restland, 1968 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Dallas, TX: Restland Mausoleum, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Dallas, TX: Trinity Oaks Church of Christ, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Dallas, TX: Tyler Street Methodist, 1974 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Fairfield, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Fairfield, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Farmers Branch, TX: Farmers Branch Church of Christ, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Farmers Branch, TX: Farmers Branch Church of Christ, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Farwell, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Fort Hood, TX: Second Armored Division, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Fort Hood, TX: The First Calvary, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Fort Worth, TX: Faith Lutheran Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Fort Worth, TX: Zion Lutheran Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Friona, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Glenn Rose, TX: Happy Hill Farms, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Houston, TX: Chapelwood United Methodist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Huntsville, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - L.L. Sams, Samples, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - L.L. Sams, Samples, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - L.L. Sams Samples, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - L.L. Sams Samples, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - L.L. Sams Samples, Canterbury, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - L.L. Sams, Samples, Capri, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Longview, TX: Apostolic Pentecostal Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Madisonville, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Marlin, TX: St. John’s Episcopal Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Midland, TX: Episcopal Church of the Holy Trinity, 1977 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Mound, TX: White Mound Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Navasota, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Port Neches, TX: First Baptist Church, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, TX: Sacred Heart Catholic Church, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - San Antonio, TX: Lackland Air Force Base Chapel, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, TX: 10th Street Methodist Church, 1979 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Waco, TX: St. Mark’s Lutheran Church, undated (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Woodway, TX: Midway Baptist Church, undated (Drawer C 13. Folder 1)
- Slides, 1976-1983, undated; 3
  The Slides series includes pieces from 1976-1983. They show the manufacturing and installation processes of the windows as well as finished products. The series is arranged chronologically and is in excellent condition.
  - General, 1977 April (Box 4 OVZ, Item 1)
  - General, 1976 December (Box 4 OVZ, Item 1)
  - General, 1977 March (Box 4 OVZ, Item 1)
  - General, 1977 May (Box 4 OVZ, Item 2)
  - General, 1983 September (Box 4 OVZ, Item 2)
  - General, undated (Box 4 OVZ, Item 1)